Welcome to the new section, the collection, so what is the collection basically once you
complete a different lateral movement from one machine to another once you achieve the
context. The next step, you will need to find what are the things you need from the organization.
It's like what kind of information you are going to upload into your cloud account.
So, I mean collecting the sensitive information like documents, employee information,
customers information or some kind of sensitive emails and sensitive documents from the
machine, so that will be very very important thing because your aim is to put a ransomware
on the machine, so the ransomware will be going to encrypt all the files in the organization,
in the machine, what you are targeting. So, if you if you encrypted all the files on the
machine, so the user, the organization cannot able to, they they they they cannot able
to open the files right because that was encrypted. So, at that time what you can do, so
you can say to the organization like your all the files are encrypted and we have we have
uploaded the file in our we have we have still some of the files the important files from
your machine and it was will be published in the cloud platform in the public platform
if you not paying the not paying the money. So, basically you are stealing some information
from the organization and you are you are you are publishing the field data into the cloud
platform. So, you need to collect the enough information, what you need like documents,
excel sheets, customers information, important password files, since to browser login
data. So, this kind of this kind of important files you need to find out in the machine.
So, we know how to use a impact at commands to interact with the machine and let us
I do not have any important file. Let me you will take a lot of time to upload ok not
a problem. So, let us target the rendial32.exe dump file from the machine. So, this
is the file we are going to we are going to collect ok this is the files we need. So, that
we are collecting this file ok. So, basically collection will be like you are going to collect
some of the information, what you need and you will be you will be zipping you will
be completely archiving the collector file because if you want this all the files you
can what you what you can do you can archiv it in one file right you can archiv it in one
file. So, if you are uploading into the cloud platform, so you can
upload the on file not in deviator file right. So, you can archiv it and you can store in
a store as a xl file and you can upload the zip file into the cloud platform mega or something.
We can we can land that first we will connect some of the files ok the rendial.
rendial32.exe dump file from the machine ok. So, from next video we can understand
how to use Vindra and collect some information without any interaction ok. So, without
you without a GUI interface ok. Let us hop off from here and we will connect you guys
in the next video see you bye bye.